You haven’t seen the facts until you’ve seen the fiction!
Pulp Fiction is a thriller, crime, comedy film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and
a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper.
Their adventures unfurl in three stories that
ingeniously trip back and forth in time.
Vincent Vega, played by John Travolta.
Jules Winnfield, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Mia Wallace, played by Uma Thurman.
Butch Coolidge, played by Bruce Willis.
Marsellus Wallace, played by Ving Rhames.
The Wolf, played by Harvey Keitel.
Music from the Motion Picture Pulp Fiction is the soundtrack to Quentin Tarantino's
1994 film Pulp Fiction, released on September 27, 1994, by MCA Records.
No traditional film score was commissioned for Pulp Fiction.
The film contains a mix of American rock and roll, surf music, pop and soul.
The soundtrack is equally untraditional, consisting of nine songs from the film, four tracks
of dialogue snippets followed by a song, and three tracks of dialogue alone.
Seven songs featured in the film were not included in
the original 41-minute soundtrack.
The album reached No.
21 on the Billboard 200, while Urge Overkill's cover of the Neil
Diamond song "Girl, You'll Be a Woman Soon" peaked at No.
59 on the Billboard Hot 100.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, stolen money, crime
boss, redemption, los angeles, california.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.